Guide to the Wright H. Everett Papers, 1853-1998 and undated RL.00376
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Business Files, 1853-1998 and undated, 27 boxes
  - Memorabilia
    - Coffee mug, My Territory, undated (Box 28)
    - Paperweight, commemorating 40th anniversary of Advertising Age, circa 1970 (Box 28)
    - Wax novelty candle, 1 Foot Candle (with General Electric logo), undated (Box 28)
- Oversize Materials, 14 boxes
  - Large Format
    - Captioned images, undated (Box 29)
    - Captioned photograph, undated (Box 29)
    - Flix examples, 1960-1970 and undated (Box 29)
    - Flix--Layout for Dow advertisement, undated (Box 29)
    - Flix--Layout for Remington Advertising house advertisement, undated (Box 29)
    - General Outdoor Advertising, approach photograph, undated (Box 29)
    - Layout, undated (Box 29)
    - Linzer paint brushes print advertisements, undated (Box 29)
    - Mounted Bovox advertisement, 1895 (Box 29)
    - Mounted photographs, undated, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Postcard mechanical, undated (Box 30)
    - Progressive Grocer, undated (Box 30)
    - Reader's Digest, 1961 (Box 30)
    - Textbook covers, 1955 and undated (Box 30)
    - Time Magazine--Layout for The Sales Picture, undated (Box 30)
    - Time Magazine--Mounted photograph, undated (Box 30)
    - Posters (Box 31)
      - The Daily Bond Crier, 1960 (Box 31)
      - The World According to Advertising Age, undated (Box 31)
  - Medium Format
    - Awards and Memorabilia (Box 32)
      - Framed antique advertisements, undated (Box 32)
      - How Were Things At The Office? Cover poster, circa 1960 (Box 32)
      - MacLean Hunter Media--Certificate of Appreciation, undated (Box 32)
      - MacLean Hunter Media--Quarter Century Club, 1990 (Box 32)
      - Progressive Grocer--Outstanding Salesmanship, 1984 (Box 32)
      - Progressive Grocer--Salesman of the Year, 1969 (Box 33)
      - Progressive Grocer--Salesman of the Year, 1969 (Box 34)
      - U.S. Department of Transportation, pilot's license, 1958 (Box 34)
    - Advertising Age--What They're (Really) Saying, 1960-1970 (Box 35)
    - American Home--Advertising orders, 1957-1959 (Box 35)
    - Clippings, 1959-1994 (Box 35)
    - Captioned photograph, undated (Box 36)
    - Captioned photograph for Clipper Magazine, undated (Box 36)
    - Drawing--Alex Webster Cuts Back As Rosie Brown Clears The Way (Robert Riger), undated (Box 36)
    - Layout, undated, 4 folders (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous film strips, undated (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Mounted design, undated (Box 36)
    - Mounted photographs, undated, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Flix examples, undated (Box 37)
    - Flix--Remington Advertising, undated (Box 37)
    - Hilton Hotels, 1960 (Box 37)
    - Marketing Magazine--So You're In The Ad Game, 1961 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous antique advertisements, 1911 and undated (Box 37)
    - W.H. Everett Co.
      - Accounts spreadsheet, 1961 (Box 37)
      - Advertisements, 1961 (Box 37)
      - Button designs, undated (Box 37)
      - McCall's Magazine, 1962 (Box 37)
      - Metropolitan Life--In The Good Old Days, undated (Box 37)
      - Promotional materials, undated (Box 37)
      - Presentation to gasoline industry, 1958 (Box 38)
      - Sales presentation to Esso, circa 1961 (Box 38)
    - Woman's Home Companion
      - Advertising orders, 1953 (Box 38)
      - Presentation on women's market, undated, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 39)
    - Printed Material
      - A&P Stores--In Trouble, 1884 (Box 40)
      - Best & Co., undated (Box 40)
      - Champion Papers--Announcing Imagination, 1964 (Box 40)
      - Champion Papers--Carnival Line, 1963 (Box 40)
      - Effingham Wilson--The Importance of Punctuality, undated (Box 40)
      - Hackley School Bulletin, undated (Box 40)
      - International Art--Good Cheer, undated (Box 40)
      - Life Magazine, 1937 Apr. 19 (Box 40)
      - Life Magazine, 1942 Apr. 6 (Box 40)
      - Life Magazine--To The Moon And Back, 1969 (Box 40)
      - McCall's Magazine, 1956 Sept. (Box 41)
      - McCall's Magazine, 1962 June (Box 41)
      - McLoughlin Bros.--Children's cutout figures, undated (Box 41)
      - Nation's Business--Brochures, undated (Box 41)
      - Patcheesy game board, undated (Box 41)
      - P.F. Collier & Sons--Prints by J.C. Leyendecker, undated (Box 41)
      - Safe Journey cutout [Caution: Very fragile], undated (Box 41)
      - Suburbia Today, 1962 (Box 41)
      - Woman's Home Companion, 1952 Feb. (Box 41)
      - Woman's Home Companion, 1956 Apr. (Box 41)
    - Printed Material (continued)
      - Advertising Age--The House That Ivory Built, 1987 (Box 42)
      - Brainstorming (Charles Clark), book advertisement proof, undated (Box 42)
      - Cultivator and Country Gentleman, 1875 Apr. 15 (Box 42)
      - Green Tiger Press--Great Advertisements calendar, 1987 (Box 42)
      - Harper's Weekly, 1867 Dec. 28 (Box 42)
      - Hobby News, 1964 Nov.-Dec. (Box 42)
      - Ladies Home Journal, 1892 Jan.-Apr. (Box 42)
      - Ladies Home Journal, 1894 May, July, Oct., Nov. (Box 42)
      - Ladies Home Journal, 1895 May-June (Box 42)
      - Ladies Home Journal, Twelve Masterpieces of Illustration [Nos. 1-4, 6, 8, 10-12 missing], undated (Box 42)
      - Poster, Salesman on Safari (Eldon Frye), undated (Box 42)
      - Standard Rate and Data Service--Business Publications Rates and Data, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Supermarket News, 1992 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1949-1990 and undated
    - Carol Belanger Grafton. 1988. Ready to Use Old-Fashioned Eating and Drinking Illustrations. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Carol Belanger Grafton. 1990. Trades and Occupations: A Pictorial Archive from Early Sources. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Cecil Hoge. 1982. Mail Order Know-How. Berkeley: Ten Speed Press. (Box 44)
    - Charles C. Gillispie, ed. 1987. A Diderot Pictorial Encyclopedia of Trades and Industry. 2 vols. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Clarence P. Hornung. 1956. Handbook of Early Advertising Art. 3rd ed. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Edgar R. Jones. 1979. Those Were the Good Old Days: A Happy Look at American Advertising, 1880-1950. New York: Simon and Schuster. (Box 44)
    - Eric Hodgins and Alan Dunn. 1959. Enough Time? The Pattern of Executive Life. New York: Doubleday. (Box 44)
    - Frank Bettger. 1949. How I Raised Myself from Failure to Success in Selling. New York: Prentice-Hall. (Box 44)
    - Gary Carey. Undated. Lost Films. New York: Museum of Modern Art. (Box 44)
    - Harper's New Monthly Magazine, vol. xxv, June-Nov. 1862. New York: Harper & Brothers. (Box 44)
    - Jackie Kannon, ed.. 1961. A Case of Humor. New York: Kanrom. (Box 44)
    - Jim Harter. 1983. Food and Drink: A Pictorial Archive from Nineteenth-Century Sources. 3rd ed. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Joe Franklin. 1959. Classics of the Silent Screen. New York: Citadel Press. (Box 44)
    - Richard Griffith and Arthur Mayer. 1970. The Movies. Revised ed. New York: Fireside. (Box 44)
    - Stanley Appelbaum. 1977. Old-Time Woodcuts from the Nineteenth-Century Stage. New York: Dover Publications. (Box 44)
    - Warren B. Meyers. 1967. Who Is That? The Late, Late Viewers Guide to the Old, Old Movie Players. New York: Personality Posters, Inc. (Box 44)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1 box
  - Alan Funt. 16mm. Unknown (Box 43)
  - Building presentation. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Early movie music and science intro. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Farris office record.Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Fast and Furious, B307, R1. Undated. Format: 8mm. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Flix, Yellow Pages and Dodge Dealers Association footage. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Media compilation. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 15:00 (Box 43)
  - Missiles and rockets, in color. Undated. Format: 8mm. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Space presentation. Undated. Format: 8mm. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Sparks presentation master. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: Unknown (Box 43)
  - Suburbia Today post-final. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 19:30 (Box 43)
  - Tobias & Olendorf, Goldblatt's 50th Anniversary Sale. Circa 1964. Format: 1" videotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)